<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coding on Whois Justin Ngo?</title>
    <link>https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/tags/coding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coding on Whois Justin Ngo?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 08:40:35 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/tags/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CSIT Mobile Reverse Engineering Mini-Challenge (CNY 2024)</title>
      <link>https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/posts/csit-cny-2024-mini-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 08:40:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/posts/csit-cny-2024-mini-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Introduction CSIT periodically releases challenges to &amp;ldquo;create awareness on the various tech focus areas of CSIT&amp;rdquo;. The topic of their CNY 2024 mini-challenge was mobile reverse engineering. I had minimal experience in this topic but I decided to give it a shot nonetheless. The following is an account of my thought process, how I understood the concepts I encountered, and how I solved the problems I encountered along the way (spoiler: G _ _ _ _ e).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OverTheWire: Leviathan</title>
      <link>https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/posts/over-the-wire-leviathan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/posts/over-the-wire-leviathan/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is my writeup for OverTheWire&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Leviathan&amp;rsquo; wargame. This is the second OverTheWire wargame I&amp;rsquo;m trying (after &amp;lsquo;Bandit&amp;rsquo;). This game is much shorter than Bandit, having only 7 levels, but, unlike Bandit, Leviathan doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any problem statements or recommended commands – you just log in to the server and find the flag somewhere on it. Leviathan is the second wargame OverTheWire recommends you to play (after Bandit), and the difficulty level is supposedly 1/10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OverTheWire: Bandit</title>
      <link>https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/posts/over-the-wire-bandit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whoisjustinngo.github.io/posts/over-the-wire-bandit/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is my writeup for OverTheWire&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Bandit&amp;rsquo; wargame, which is essentially a capture the flag (CTF) challenge with the flag in each level being a password you&amp;rsquo;ll need to ssh into the next level. Each level has a problem statement indicating the location of the password on the server, in addition to some useful commands one might need to retrieve it.
Please look at the OverTheWire Bandit website for the problem statements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
